Yes friends, the central bank Fed has
issued a commentary three days ago
and in a way, it was a very important
commentary which will decide the future direction of the market.
Friends,
in this commentary, they have taken a
U-turn on their own stand, which they were saying earlier
that they are not going to raise interest rates till 2024.
They have withdrawn that stand and have now said that
inflation is also increasing with growth. This could be a
matter of conditions and it is possible
that from 2023 they can increase their interest rates
on bonds. Friends, when the interest rate
increases in the US Federal Bank, it
increases in its bonds. So, whatever money is there in the emerging stock
market like India's stock market,
foreign money, that is,
through SAF and SBI, automatically starts going
back into Yes bonds
because they can see more attractive returns there. So,
in the coming days, it is possible that the
validation of the trend is going to increase and there is going to be
pressure on commodities.  Like
steel and metal, the prices are going to come down and
rationalize and that is why
in the coming days you will
see pressure in stocks like steel, metal etc.
Well, in whichever stock there
is a lot of holding of FI, slowly slowly
Saifai is going to withdraw his money,
so friends, at such a time,
what stop can be very good for you in such a contract
which has
fundamental value, technical indication is
saying f5, take it almost nice, it
is the best one and don't care, due to dollar there is
not going to be any much benefit adverse effect in them, so
we are going to talk about such a stock, it is going to be a very
good video because after doing a lot of
research we have found the stock for you,
so you should watch this video completely, it is going to be a
very good learning
for you, so go ahead,
first let me tell you one thing, if you
want to learn something in the stock market in a genuine way and want to run along with learning,
then subscribe
to Hotspots now because we will always bring such videos for
you continuously  If we keep bringing it, then it will be brought sooner or later.
Friends, the
company we are going to talk about
is a market leader and it is in the
non-life insurance business, friends, that is,
not the life insurance business, but
apart from that, it acts in any insurance business.
If you look at its market cap, it is
around 2800. Its current market
price is ₹100.70. If you look at the book value, it is
one hundred and fifty-five rupees. So,
friends, the current
market price is very close to the valley. It is
very good according to the calibration.
And if you talk about its past, it
is 17.4 copies. Friends, this company itself has been
trending for the last four years. It is
trading at a PE of about 23 on
average. But its speed right now is
very low. So, we are
seeing a very attractive elevation. The
average speed in the market is above ₹25.
You know, friends, the speed of Nifty
today is around 3132. So,
in every parameter.
According to the calibration, we see a very good and
attractive opportunity for investment.
Yes, if you look at it from RO, it is
close to nine percent. But friends, as
I told you earlier,
in financial and non-financial businesses, etc.,
its growth rate is higher than the accused, growth rate in profit,
etc., these parameters
matter a lot, but this is positive, this
thing in itself is satisfactory.
Friends, if we talk about this, the annual sales of
this company is 3300 crores and the market cap
is 2900, that is, the market cap is less than this, so
how good is the market cap valuation that is
available here, friends, its
net worth is 2500 crores, so almost the
market cap is the same and the reserves are the same, friends,
so this is making a very good deadly combination for
it. Yes, right now you can ask one thing
that okay, today the finances
seem good, but how are the future growth
prospects and how the company has performed
in the last two to three years, that is
also important, so I will tell you this also in the
past.  In two-three years, the company's
profit has almost doubled.
Friends, if we look at it, there is a Boeing company,
friends, if
you look at the companies listed in the insurance business, then there is HDFC Life,
SBI Life, ICICI Prudential Life
Insurance Album, but there is New India
Assurance. Although HDFC and SBI
Life, friends, and ICICI Prudential
Life are in the real life insurance business,
but still, because there are less listed companies,
we will cut it as well. So, friends,
if you compare the elevation here, first of all,
you look at the PE ratio. HDFC
Life has a period of one and a half times,
SBI has 68, such as
Torch Light is 11015, and such as Aircel is
around 47,000. So, friends, it is a very
reasonable elevation of poached eggs. If you
look at the market cap here also according to sales and profit, then there too, New
India Insurance will appear to be performing very well on the
basis of valuation. You can see here,
friends, this is a profit of sixteen hundred crores,
and to that, the market cap is almost
Seventeen times are the times of net
profit of any company. Now
see friends, it is about hundred
times city to hundred times as much as
market conditions to versus profit. If we
also look at the profit margin, because
friends, many people may have a thought that if it is a
government company, then it will
not be efficient, its profit margin will
not be that good, but here a case
seems to be happening in reverse, friends, if you
look at New India Assurance, the
profit margin is 6 percent, from which other
companies like HDFC Life 1.65,
SBI Life Insurance for only
less than one percent,
companies are seen coming in the top 10 spots, so all in all, at
this lowest level of financial parameters, as well as comparative elevation, we are
finding it very good. Now if we
explain its P or not, it
means whether P will increase in the future, whether profit will
increase or not, then its text will have to be
kept in growth and future prospect will be seen,
if we talk about its earlier finances, then
you can see here
friends, in the insurance business
More than sales because we are not selling a product or service,
here we are
selling insurance policies. So, how much loss are you
incurring, how much risk are you taking, how
risky insurance are you selling to people, is
very important because it is
generally believed that the
claim settlement ratio in government companies is very
high, hence they remain loss-making.
Therefore, here you will see that if
we have any objection to these in profit, then
if you
look at the net profit growth of the last 3 years, friends, there is a 70%
CAGR, which means that the
company's profit almost doubles in two to two and a half years. If
you look at the last time, then the profit has increased almost
two and a half times. If we talk about the three-year
sales cross, that is, policy sales,
friends, then it is 13 percent and
senior, according to me, one of the very
good in this sector, it is available. If we
talk about the stock price, friends, then
in the last 3 years, it has given an eight percent negative
return. Friends, this is the
opportunity of such divergence, such difference.
What we have to tap, I had
told you earlier also that the company which is highly
growing is fundamentally leading but the stock
price is low, that is, the market has
not yet discovered its value,
we have to identify such stocks and
put a long wait in it and
you should hold it for investment because it can
give you tremendous returns, so
friends, now we will see about its financials'
sales and profit,
I can see here friends,
I am taking it in 2018 because when this company was
listed, the sales were around Rs 9000 crore
and in front of that it has increased almost two times,
today if you can see this almost
double in two and a half years, if we
talk about operating profit, friends, then
from glass we have come into profit and you
can see operating profit is life time only, so life
time high sales, friends, there is life
time profit, there is operating profit,
yes if we talk about petty net profit, then there is
profit of Rs 60 crore, friends,
acid in stomach and  It is almost life time. This
2190 professional boxer that we see is
an item infected by the government
because if you see, the
operating profit is at the end here,
yet there is a profit here, so on the opposite side
by the government, so you cannot consider it as a
profit, but if you see here, there is
profit here on a truly operating and net basis, so
life time high sales, life time
cooperative
profit and life time net profit, so
friends, now we will see that it is
trading at a life time high price
because when we look at the fundamentals,
friends, we invest the fundamentals in the price section in the same way
that
where is this top adding on the life time price,
friends, let us look at its share holding pattern,
a person or you can see, as I
told you earlier, 25 percent
is the stock of the Government of India and
who comes under the Government of India, so you can see here that
this is by the President of India,
in that is the State by Government, normal
government company.  Friends, this is a trick, it is
folded by the President of India,
and here you will see that FI
is almost more than nil, if
FI completely goes back, leaves India, leaves the
emerging market stock market and goes
back to the US, even then it is
not going to be too self-owned in the company, there is no
problem, this is the thirty percent
stake, friends, and the public, the general public
like us, is 1.34%, this trick
means that the public has a very less stake,
friends, so here also
we are not seeing any such self-owned problem, after the retail investors get into panic, there is no such problem
here, that the downside is that
friends, it seems to be very limited, it
is a highly growing company and still
attractive elevation and lower PI is available,
so MB in one of the
prosperity to invest in the stock
register of the country, we also talk about the technical,
so here on the wheat trading website
and here I have opened the chart of
New India Assurance and this is the
depression that I have taken, time setting.  It has been done on a
weekly basis
because we are talking about a long depression
investment here. You
can see friends, ever since the stock was listed on
21-3-2018,
we have seen a continuous downfall in this stock,
but if you look at the sections of the last few sessions, the
last few months, then a clear
cut is visible, this means that for
one thing, it is
forming a grinding pattern in a very long time. If you
look at the second thing clearly, then a cup and
handle pattern will be seen forming in it,
you can see this, this is a cup and this handle
pattern, it is a very reliable pattern,
specifically friends, when
you will see its breakout with volume and the
second thing I would like to tell you
friends, right
now the breakout is of a long depression, for example,
suppose if you look here, the
stock was spreading in the same range in this parameter for one year
and after that, now we
see a breakout, that is,
you can see a breakout of about one year here, so that is how much the
stock has risen.  The
chances of going up increase because that
fragrance becomes very inherently
strong. If we talk about volume,
friends, then
before forming a handle,
you will see the volume, so country volume
watch live time only volume, almost lifetime
volume, here a break point has been found and
right now the handle is being formed, friends, the
volume in it is also quite good, it is seeing
better volume than the average volume at that time, so the
price here at 173 is exactly the price at resistance,
friends, as soon as it
goes above 174 175 with Bollywood in a good way
and a strong leader, can go up to its
lifetime high price Rs. 31030
daily two times and how much
depression can be felt in it, friends,
if I talk about the technical chart pattern in this, then the amount of
depression that was felt for the formation of the cup, that is, almost 1 year
in the convention, it can go
back to its lifetime high in the same year and the
second thing that we have shown here friends is the
fundamentals  They are also supporting
because there is lifetime high sales, there is lifetime
profit, there is lifetime operating
profit, so all these parameters are
supporting that if there is lifetime then the
price of the city is formed, friends, so this is a complete
analysis of very good and
excellent investment opportunity
stocks, friends, if you also want to invest in a multibagger
or long term investment, then the
point to be done is to
invest in the metro parameter
and after that, in the same parameter, you have to estimate the sector
and the company, you have to
invest in it with its peers, the day
you find a growing company with
reasonable valuation from its peers,
where the market has
not yet given it a good elevation relative to it, that will be
your stock, a multibagger and for long
term investment, I hope friends,
you liked this video, if you
like this video then please hit the like button
and keep subscribing to such good insightful Lipika
videos,
thank you and there are more such
profitable stocks  Stay with Little Girl Video
in the next video